Elections Research Center Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Elections Research Center Records 1918-1992 1932-1992
MSS78897
Elections Research Center (Governmental Affairs Institute)
110,000 items
312 containers plus 1 oversize
126 linear feet
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Nonprofit elections research and analysis organization. Newspaper clippings, ballots, election returns, reports, notes, statistical data, correspondence, and printed material documents elections in all fifty states and the District of Columbia collected by the organization between 1955 and 1992 for the purpose of compilation, analysis, and publication.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Wallace, George C. (George Corley), 1919-1998.
Organizations
District of Columbia. Board of Elections.; Elections Research Center (Governmental Affairs Institute); United States. Congress.
Subjects
Apportionment (Election law)--United States.; Elections--Germany.; Elections--Great Britain.; Elections--Poland.; Elections--Research--United States.; Elections--Soviet Union.; Elections--United States.; Home rule--Washington (D.C.); Political parties--United States.; Prohibition--Oklahoma.; Segregation in education--United States.; Voting research--United States.; Voting--United States.
Places
United States--Census, 1990.; United States--Politics and government--20th century.; Washington (D.C.)--Politics and government.
Acquisition Information
The Elections Research Center Records were given to the Library of Congress by the Center's director, Richard Scammon, in 1989. A supplement was given by Richard Scammon's estate in 1999.
Other Repositories
Other records of the Elections Research Center can be found at the John F. Kennedy Library, Boston, Massachusetts.
Access and Restrictions
The Elections Research Center Records are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Organizational History
The Elections Research Center was established in 1955 as a branch of the Governmental Affairs Institute, a nonprofit research and survey organization founded in 1950. After receiving a grant from the Stern Family Fund, then Chairman of the Board, Edward Litchfield, invited noted political scientist, Richard M. Scammon, to head the Institute’s newly formed Elections Office, later known as the Elections Research Center. The Elections Research Center operated under Scammon’s direction for thirty years, collecting elections data from each state at the municipal, state, and federal level and publishing several comprehensive analyses of American voting trends and statistics. Using the data collected, the Center published its biennial series, America Votes, first released in 1956 and thereafter each general election, which systematically reported voting returns by state. Other works edited by Scammon, with assistance from his collaborator, Alice B. McGillivray, under the auspices of the Elections Research Center include Southern Primaries 58 (1959), America at the Polls: A Handbook of American Presidential and Election Statistics, 1920-1964 (1965), and America at the Polls: A Handbook of American Presidential and Election Statistics, 1968-1984 (1988). The Elections Research Center closed in 1995.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the Elections Research Center span the years 1918-1992, with the bulk of the material concentrated between 1932 and 1992. The records consist of newspaper clippings, ballots, election returns, reports, notes, statistical data, voting district maps, printed material, and correspondence. The collection is arranged, filed, and numbered as received from the donor and organized into a General File, State File and Oversize.
The General File contains newspaper clippings, ballots, notes, and correspondence covering a variety of topics, namely voting and election matters of broad national and international interest. The material includes newspaper clippings documenting national coverage of the 1980 general election, the 1990 Census and resulting congressional reapportionment, and printed material regarding the 99th through 101st Congresses, among other topics. Newspaper clippings and printed materials regarding elections in Poland, Germany, Great Britain, and the Soviet Union are also comprised in this series, as are subject files regarding politician George C. Wallace. The correspondence in this series largely pertains to expenditures and funding requests for a voter registration project conducted by the Center between 1973 and 1977.
More extensive in scope and chronology is the State File, which contains newspaper clippings from local news outlets, sample ballots, notes compiled by Scammon, voting district maps, statistical data, and printed materials covering election campaigns and outcomes for all fifty states and the District of Columbia. Within each state is documentation of the biennial primary and general elections, which for most states ranges between 1956 and 1992. Some states, though not all, include separate coverage of gubernatorial and municipal elections, dating primarily from the early 1950s until the mid-1980s. Election returns and voting statistics by district for major American cities, including New York City, Philadelphia, Pittsburgh, Los Angeles, San Francisco, and Chicago, among others, is also comprised within the State File. Of particular note are the sample ballots collected for several states, the majority of which date between 1932 and 1948 and illustrate the variety of mid-twentieth century American political parties and their logos. Significant ballot measures chronicled in this series include Oklahoma’s repeal of prohibition in 1959, and Virginia, North Carolina, and other states' attempts to maintain and later eliminate segregation in public schools. Also of note is a file pertaining to the creation of the District of Columbia's Board of Elections in 1955 and later, correspondence regarding the establishment of Home Rule in the District in 1973, for which Scammon served as a consultant.
With the exception of one file regarding the Stern Family Fund grant for a voter registration project in the General File, this collection does not document the Elections Research Center’s business operations or functions, nor does it chronical publication processes for the America Votes series or any other of the Center’s printed volumes. The collection does however serve as a comprehensive database of voting statistics throughout the United States for nearly half of the twentieth century. The inclusion of local newspaper clippings furthermore provides a local perspective on election matters at the voting district level.
Arrangement of the Papers
This collection is arranged in three series:
General File, 1930-1992
State File, 1918-1992
Oversize, 1959-1987
Container List
- General File, 1930-1992 (Box 1-12)
  Newspaper clippings, ballots, notes, correspondence, and printed material.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Ballots, 1980-1988, (4 folders) (Box 1)
  - Chronological file (Box 2)
    - 1930-1944 (includes data concerning elctions from 1894 to 1944), (16 folders)
    - 1956 (Box 2)
    - 1980, (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - 1980, (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - 1980, (4 folders) (Box 5)
    - 1980, (4 folders) (Box 6)
    - 1981-1984, (4 folders) (Box 7)
    - 1986-1990, (5 folders) (Box 8)
    - 1992, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Congressional miscellany, 1957-1985, undated (Box 9)
  - Germany, 1946-1982, undated (Box 9)
  - Great Britain, House of Commons, 1970-1974 (Box 9)
  - Poland, 1956-1969 (Box 9)
  - Presidential election miscellany, 1932-1989 (Box 10)
  - Proportional representation, 1945-1983, undated (Box 10)
  - Puerto Rico, 1955-1990, (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Russia/Soviet Union, 1989-1993 (Box 11)
  - Standard Metropolitan Areas, 1955-1957 (Box 11)
  - Stern Fund Registration Project, 1973-1977 (Box 11)
  - Wallace, George C. (Box 11)
    - 1964-1972, (5 folders) (Box 11)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 12)
- State File, 1918-1992 (Box 12-312)
  Newspaper clippings, ballots, notes, voting district maps, statistical data, and printed materials.
  Arranged alphabetically by state.
  - Alabama (Box 12)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 12)
      - 1956-1962, (9 folders) (Box 12)
      - 1964-1968, (7 folders) (Box 13)
      - 1970-1974, (10 folders) (Box 14)
      - 1976-1984, (17 folders) (Box 15)
      - 1986-1989, (7 folders) (Box 16)
      - 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 17)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1963-1969, 1979-1983, (6 folders) (Box 17)
    - Miscellany, 1936-1984, (3 folders) (Box 17)
  - Alaska (Box 18)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 18)
      - 1956-1966, (12 folders) (Box 18)
      - 1968-1976, (12 folders) (Box 19)
      - 1978-1986, (10 folders) (Box 20)
      - 1988-1992, (4 folders) (Box 21)
    - Miscellany, 1946-1984, (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Arizona (Box 21)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 21)
      - 1956-1958, (4 folders) (Box 21)
      - 1960-1970, (13 folders) (Box 22)
      - 1972-1980, (10 folders) (Box 23)
      - 1982-1992, (11 folders) (Box 24)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections, 1988-1991 (Box 24)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1961 (Box 24)
    - Miscellany (Box 24)
      - 1920-1948 (Box 24)
      - 1953-1975, (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Arkansas (Box 25)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 25)
      - 1956-1961, (8 folders) (Box 25)
      - 1962-1970, (9 folders) (Box 26)
      - 1970-1976, (12 folders) (Box 27)
      - 1978-1986, (15 folders) (Box 28)
      - 1988-1992, (8 folders) (Box 29)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1957-1959, (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - Miscellany, 1933-1976 (Box 29)
  - California (Box 30)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 30)
      - 1956-1960, (6 folders) (Box 30)
      - 1962-1964, (5 folders) (Box 31)
      - 1964-1968, (7 folders) (Box 32)
      - 1968-1972, (7 folders) (Box 33)
      - 1972-1974, (6 folders) (Box 34)
      - 1974-1976, (6 folders) (Box 35)
      - 1978-1980, (6 folders) (Box 36)
      - 1980-1982, (6 folders) (Box 37)
      - 1982-1984, (7 folders) (Box 38)
      - 1986-1987, (4 folders) (Box 39)
      - 1988-1992, (6 folders) (Box 40)
      - 1992, (3 folders) (Box 41)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections, 1978 (Box 41)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections (Box 41)
      - 1955-1961, (4 folders) (Box 41)
      - 1963-1973, (7 folders) (Box 42)
      - 1973-1985, (8 folders) (Box 43)
    - Miscellany (Box 43)
      - 1952-1983, (4 folders) (Box 43)
      - 1963-1974, (5 folders) (Box 44)
      - 1973-1983, (5 folders) (Box 45)
  - Colorado (Box 45)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 45)
      - 1956, (2 folders) (Box 45)
      - 1958-1968, (12 folders) (Box 46)
      - 1970-1978, (9 folders) (Box 47)
      - 1978-1988, (11 folders) (Box 48)
      - 1988-1992, (4 folders) (Box 49)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1955-1971, (4 folders) (Box 49)
    - Miscellany, 1932-1989, (3 folders) (Box 49)
  - Connecticut (Box 49)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 49)
      - 1956, (2 folders) (Box 49)
      - 1958-1968, (13 folders) (Box 50)
      - 1970-1976, (9 folders) (Box 51)
      - 1978-1984, (9 folders) (Box 52)
      - 1984-1992, (11 folders) (Box 53)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1963 (Box 54)
    - Miscellany, 1933-1981, (4 folders) (Box 54)
  - Delaware (Box 54)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 54)
      - 1956-1962, (9 folders) (Box 54)
      - 1964-1972, (12 folders) (Box 55)
      - 1974-1990, (18 folders) (Box 56)
      - 1992 (Box 57)
    - Miscellany, 1957-1983, (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - Florida (Box 57)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 57)
      - 1956-1958, (5 folders) (Box 57)
      - 1960-1966, (7 folders) (Box 58)
      - 1966-1972, (8 folders) (Box 59)
      - 1972-1976, (8 folders) (Box 60)
      - 1976-1980, (10 folders) (Box 61)
      - 1980-1988, (13 folders) (Box 62)
      - 1988-1992, (5 folders) (Box 63)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1961-1965, 1985, (3 folders) (Box 63)
    - Miscellany (Box 63)
      - 1920-1983, (2 folders) (Box 63)
      - 1952-1977, (3 folders) (Box 64)
  - Georgia (Box 64)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 64)
      - 1956-1958, (6 folders) (Box 64)
      - 1960-1965, (7 folders) (Box 65)
      - 1966-1968, (5 folders) (Box 66)
      - 1970-1972, (7 folders) (Box 67)
      - 1974-1976, (8 folders) (Box 68)
      - 1977-1980, (8 folders) (Box 69)
      - 1982-1984, (9 folders) (Box 70)
      - 1986-1992, (9 folders) (Box 71)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1957-1981, (7 folders) (Box 72)
    - Miscellany, 1932-1982, (5 folders) (Box 72)
  - Hawaii (Box 73)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 73)
      - 1956-1964 See also Oversize, (11 folders) (Box 73)
      - 1966-1972, (8 folders) (Box 74)
      - 1972-1978, (9 folders) (Box 75)
      - 1978-1986, (12 folders) (Box 76)
      - 1986-1990, (8 folders) (Box 77)
      - 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 78)
    - Miscellany, 1946-1985, (3 folders) (Box 78)
  - Idaho (Box 78)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 78)
      - 1956-1962, (8 folders) (Box 78)
      - 1964-1974, (12 folders) (Box 79)
      - 1976-1984, (13 folders) (Box 80)
      - 1986-1992, (7 folders) (Box 81)
    - Miscellany, 1920-1973, (4 folders) (Box 81)
  - Illinois (Box 81)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 81)
      - 1956-1958, (6 folders) (Box 81)
      - 1960-1966, (8 folders) (Box 82)
      - 1966-1972, (9 folders) (Box 83)
      - 1972-1976, (9 folders) (Box 84)
      - 1976-1980, (7 folders) (Box 85)
      - 1980-1984, (9 folders) (Box 86)
      - 1986-1988, (8 folders) (Box 87)
      - 1990-1992, (4 folders) (Box 88)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections (Box 88)
      - 1952-1983, (5 folders) (Box 88)
      - 1967-1987, (8 folders) (Box 89)
      - 1989 (Box 90)
    - Miscellany (Box 90)
      - 1923, 1932-1978, (2 folders) (Box 90)
      - 1946-1988, (6 folders) (Box 91)
      - 1969-1986, (2 folders) (Box 92)
  - Indiana (Box 92)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 92)
      - 1956-1962, (9 folders) (Box 92)
      - 1964-1970, (8 folders) (Box 93)
      - 1970-1976, (9 folders) (Box 94)
      - 1978-1984, (10 folders) (Box 95)
      - 1984-1992, (10 folders) (Box 96)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1955-1987, (11 folders) (Box 97)
    - Miscellany (Box 97)
      - 1932-1958, undated, (4 folders) (Box 97)
      - 1960-1985, undated, (3 folders) (Box 98)
  - Iowa (Box 98)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 98)
      - 1956-1959, (5 folders) (Box 98)
      - 1960-1968, (10 folders) (Box 99)
      - 1968-1976, (10 folders) (Box 100)
      - 1978-1982, (8 folders) (Box 101)
      - 1984-1992, (11 folders) (Box 102)
    - Miscellany, 1932-1977, (3 folders) (Box 103)
  - Kansas (Box 103)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 103)
      - 1956-1960, (6 folders) (Box 103)
      - 1962-1974, (13 folders) (Box 104)
      - 1974-1982, (10 folders) (Box 105)
      - 1984-1992, (9 folders) (Box 106)
    - Miscellany (Box 106)
      - 1932-1958 (Box 106)
      - 1945-1978, (5 folders) (Box 107)
  - Kentucky (Box 108)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 108)
      - 1956-1974, (20 folders) (Box 108)
      - 1976-1986, (14 folders) (Box 109)
      - 1988-1992, (6 folders) (Box 110)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections (Box 110)
      - 1955-1959, (6 folders) (Box 110)
      - 1963-1979, (10 folders) (Box 111)
      - 1979-1991, (5 folders) (Box 112)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1954-1969, (5 folders) (Box 112)
    - Miscellany, 1932-1987, (3 folders) (Box 112)
  - Louisiana (Box 113)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 113)
      - 1956-1960, (11 folders) (Box 113)
      - 1960-1964, (10 folders) (Box 114)
      - 1965-1972, (13 folders) (Box 115)
      - 1972-1978, (13 folders) (Box 116)
      - 1980-1988, (17 folders) (Box 117)
      - 1990-1992, (5 folders) (Box 118)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections (Box 118)
      - 1963-1971, (4 folders) (Box 118)
      - 1971-1983, (6 folders) (Box 119)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1950-1986, (10 folders) (Box 120)
    - Miscellany (Box 120)
      - 1920-1985, (4 folders) (Box 120)
      - 1955-1977, (3 folders) (Box 121)
  - Maine (Box 122)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 122)
      - 1956-1968, (15 folders) (Box 122)
      - 1970-1978, (11 folders) (Box 123)
      - 1980-1992, (12 folders) (Box 124)
    - Miscellany (Box 124)
      - 1933-1956 (Box 124)
      - 1948-1985, (3 folders) (Box 125)
  - Maryland (Box 125)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 125)
      - 1956-1962, (9 folders) (Box 125)
      - 1964-1972, (10 folders) (Box 126)
      - 1972-1974, (6 folders) (Box 127)
      - 1976-1978, (6 folders) (Box 128)
      - 1980-1984, (9 folders) (Box 129)
      - 1986-1992, (10 folders) (Box 130)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1951-1983, (8 folders) (Box 131)
    - Miscellany (Box 131)
      - 1920-1980, (4 folders) (Box 131)
      - 1950-1986, (4 folders) (Box 132)
  - Massachusetts (Box 132)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 132)
      - 1956, (3 folders) (Box 132)
      - 1958-1966, (11 folders) (Box 133)
      - 1968-1972, (9 folders) (Box 134)
      - 1974-1980, (9 folders) (Box 135)
      - 1980-1988, (12 folders) (Box 136)
      - 1990-1992, (6 folders) (Box 137)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections, 1974 (Box 138)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1952-1983, (15 folders) (Box 138)
    - Miscellany (Box 138)
      - 1932-1985, (2 folders) (Box 138)
      - 1956-1985, (6 folders) (Box 139)
      - 1984-1988, (2 folders) (Box 140)
  - Michigan (Box 140)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 140)
      - 1955-1956, (3 folders) (Box 140)
      - 1958-1964, (11 folders) (Box 141)
      - 1964-1970, (7 folders) (Box 142)
      - 1970-1973, (6 folders) (Box 143)
      - 1974-1976, (8 folders) (Box 144)
      - 1978-1982, (9 folders) (Box 145)
      - 1984-1992, (10 folders) (Box 146)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections, 1963 (Box 147)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1937-1988, (11 folders) (Box 147)
    - Miscellany (Box 147)
      - 1932-1982, (2 folders) (Box 147)
      - 1954-1985, (6 folders) (Box 148)
  - Minnesota (Box 149)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 149)
      - 1956-1964, (12 folders) (Box 149)
      - 1966-1976, (12 folders) (Box 150)
      - 1976-1982, (8 folders) (Box 151)
      - 1984-1990, (7 folders) (Box 152)
      - 1992 (Box 153)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections (Box 153)
      - 1931-1985, (7 folders) (Box 153)
      - 1952-1971, (18 folders) (Box 154)
      - 1972-1985, (12 folders) (Box 155)
    - Miscellany (Box 155)
      - 1918-1978, (4 folders) (Box 155)
      - 1936-1985, (5 folders) (Box 156)
      - 1954-1986, (5 folders) (Box 157)
  - Mississippi (Box 158)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 158)
      - 1956-1972, (20 folders) (Box 158)
      - 1974-1986, (20 folders) (Box 159)
      - 1988-1992, (7 folders) (Box 160)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections (Box 160)
      - 1955-1967, (8 folders) (Box 160)
      - 1971-1983, (11 folders) (Box 161)
      - 1987-1991, (2 folders) (Box 162)
    - Miscellany, 1920-1982, (7 folders) (Box 162)
  - Missouri (Box 162)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 162)
      - 1956-1958, (4 folders) (Box 162)
      - 1959-1970, (13 folders) (Box 163)
      - 1972-1980, (10 folders) (Box 164)
      - 1982-1988, (9 folders) (Box 165)
      - 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 166)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1955-1985, (17 folders) (Box 166)
    - Miscellany (Box 166)
      - 1932-1982, (2 folders) (Box 166)
      - 1946-1982, (6 folders) (Box 167)
      - 1969-1992, (3 folders) (Box 168)
  - Montana (Box 168)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 168)
      - 1956-1958, (4 folders) (Box 168)
      - 1960-1974, (17 folders) (Box 169)
      - 1976-1986, (15 folders) (Box 170)
      - 1988-1992, (6 folders) (Box 171)
    - Miscellany, 1920-1962, circa 1984, undated, (3 folders) (Box 171)
  - Nebraska (Box 171)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 171)
      - 1920-1924, 1944-1948 (Box 171)
      - 1950-1964, (11 folders) (Box 172)
      - 1966-1974, (9 folders) (Box 173)
      - 1974-1982, (11 folders) (Box 174)
      - 1984-1992, (11 folders) (Box 175)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1964-1969, 1981, (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - Miscellany, 1932-1962, 1973-1987, (3 folders) (Box 175)
  - Nevada (Box 175)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 175)
      - 1930-1954 (Box 175)
      - 1956-1964, (10 folders) (Box 176)
      - 1966-1972, (7 folders) (Box 177)
      - 1972-1980, (11 folders) (Box 178)
      - 1982-1992, (10 folders) (Box 179)
    - Miscellany, 1920-1963, (3 folders) (Box 180)
  - New Hampshire (Box 180)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 180)
      - 1956-1964, (10 folders) (Box 180)
      - 1964-1972, (12 folders) (Box 181)
      - 1972-1976, (10 folders) (Box 182)
      - 1976-1984, (10 folders) (Box 183)
      - 1984-1990, (10 folders) (Box 184)
      - 1992, (2 folders) (Box 185)
    - Miscellany, 1932-1987 See also Oversize, (5 folders) (Box 185)
  - New Jersey (Box 186)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 186)
      - 1956-1966, (12 folders) (Box 186)
      - 1968-1976, (11 folders) (Box 187)
      - 1978-1988, (16 folders) (Box 188)
      - 1989-1992, (4 folders) (Box 189)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections (Box 189)
      - 1955-1967, (10 folders) (Box 189)
      - 1969-1985, (10 folders) (Box 190)
      - 1989 (Box 191)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1950-1978, (11 folders) (Box 191)
    - Miscellany (Box 191)
      - 1928-1957 (Box 191)
      - 1932-1981, (6 folders) (Box 192)
  - New Mexico (Box 192)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 192)
      - 1956-1958, (5 folders) (Box 192)
      - 1960-1970, (13 folders) (Box 193)
      - 1972-1982 See also Oversize, (13 folders) (Box 194)
      - 1984-1992 See also Oversize, (11 folders) (Box 195)
  - New York (Box 195)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 195)
      - 1956, (2 folders) (Box 195)
      - 1958-1962, (11 folders) (Box 196)
      - 1962-1967, (7 folders) (Box 197)
      - 1968-1970, (7 folders) (Box 198)
      - 1970-1976, (8 folders) (Box 199)
      - 1976-1980, (8 folders) (Box 200)
      - 1980-1986, (10 folders) (Box 201)
      - 1986-1992, (10 folders) (Box 202)
    - Gubernatorial and state elections, 1963-1971, (3 folders) (Box 202)
    - Mayoral and municipal elections, 1957-1977, (8 folders) (Box 203)
    - Miscellany (Box 203)
      - 1932-1983, (6 folders) (Box 203)
      - 1952-1985, (8 folders) (Box 204)
    - New York City (Box 204)
      - Mayoral and municipal elections (Box 204)
        - 1957-1961, (5 folders) (Box 204)
        - 1963-1970, (8 folders) (Box 205)
        - 1973-1985, (8 folders) (Box 206)
        - 1989-1993, (2 folders) (Box 207)
      - Miscellany (Box 207)
        - 1929-1986, (6 folders) (Box 207)
        - 1968-1976, (2 folders) (Box 208)
  - North Carolina (Box 208)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 208)
      - 1956-1960, (7 folders) (Box 208)
      - 1962-1972, (14 folders) (Box 209)
      - 1974-1980, (13 folders) (Box 210)
      - 1982-1988, (13 folders) (Box 211)
      - 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 212)
    - Miscellany, 1933-1986, (2 folders) (Box 212)
  - North Dakota (Box 212)
    - General elections and primaries (Box 212)
      - 1956-1960, (6 folders) (Box 212)
      - 1962-1972, (12 folders) (Box 213)
      - 1974-1986, (15 folders) (Box 214)
      - 1988-1992, (5 folders) (Box 215)